Finding aid for the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archive Collection of Audio Materials, 1970-1999 LSC.2230
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Conference Cassettes, 1972-1999; Series 11.; 34 audio cassette tapes
  - Eco-Feminist Conference at University of Southern California: Gloria Orenstein, Reinvoking the Grove, March 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 1)
    Recording of talks at Eco-feminist Conference at USC, beginning with Brian Swimme, on the origin of galaxies. "Ecofeminism" is an activist and academic movement that sees connections between the domination of nature and the exploitation of women.
  - Eco-Feminist Conference at University of Southern California: Cosmology of the Goddess, March 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 2)
    Speakers, Charlene Spretnak and Brian Swimme, discuss creation of the universe and share ideas, from archaeological evidence, about myths of goddess, nature-based religion. Also look at how male gods took over as the most powerful in ancient mythology, focusing on Aphrodite's role as goddess.
  - Eco-Feminist Conference at University of Southern California: What is Eco-feminism, Issues and Visions, 27 March 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 3-4)
    Opening plenary of Eco-Feminist Conference with speakers, Gloria Orenstein, Charlene Spretnak, Susan Griffin, and Paula Gunn Allen. Recording begins with a welcome to all participants in the conference. Topics include: the significance of the goddess, re-identifying creation in the image of the woman, eco-feminism definitions, and goals of eco-feminism.
  - Terry Wolverton / Mary Lynn Hughes: Anti-Racism, 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 5)
    KPFK radio show, Feminist Magazine interview with Terry Wolverton and Mary Lynn Hughes, where they discuss racism and the issue: white men have created environment of sexual tension to control white women and black men as a set up for white man's advantage. Danger of manipulation by white men through use of racism. Institutionalized racism is another topic, due to lack of exposure to diversity.
  - National Lesbian Conference: Walk That Talk Ethics Workshop, 8 October 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 6)
    2nd Annual Lesbian Conference organized by the National Organization for Women. Yvonne King and Geni Cowan are speakers and they facilitate group discussion and small group sharing out with audience. Topics include: definitions for ethics, situations which challenged personal values and ethics, homophobia, racism, how to move forward and handle homophobia and racism.
  - National Lesbian Conference: Future Workshop, Tape 1 of 2, 10 October 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 7)
    National Organization for Women's National Lesbian Conference in San Diego, CA. Workshop speakers are Charlotte Bunch, Melinda Paras, and Carmen Vasquez. Recording includes poetry reading, statement of goals for conference, and speakers' perspectives on being "out" as lesbians and the support systems, networks, and/or movements needed to allow lesbians to be strong and successful women.
    Tape 2 in Various Topics Cassettes series, Box 1, Folder 5.
  - National Lesbian Conference: Question of Privacy, October 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 8)
    National Organization for Women's National Lesbian Conference held in San Diego. Key speaker is Susan McGreivy. Topics discussed include: patriarchal law, reproductive law, religious undertones in law, the concept of the functional family, and feminist independence.
    Sound becomes unintelligible at minute 37 of Side 1.
  - Spring Conference of Gay/Lesbian Health Association: Looking Past Addictive Behavior, 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 9)
    Recording of Looking Past Addictive Behavior panel at the Gay/Lesbian Health Association's Spring Conference in Los Angeles. Discussion on addiction, the issues and problems raised, personality structures that support addiction, treatments, and relapses.
  - Rape City Mall, May 1977; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 10)
    Rape City Mall took place in Los Angeles, CA, for three weeks in May, 1977, and was an event meant to bring to the forefront and end the rape of women through art installations, performances, interviews, and demonstrations. Recording of interviews with public as they pass by and react to art installation piece, "Three Weeks in May," by Suzanne Lacy. Interviewees ask questions about locations, express shock, and share personal stories.
    Audio goes in and out in volume and clarity.
  - Parents & Friends of Gays, The Kinsey Institute: Exploring the roots of homosexuality, 20 October 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 11)
    Recording of Parents & Friends of Gays meeting at the Kinsey Institute, with speaker, Dr. Martin Weinberg of Indiana University. Dr. Weinberg explains conclusions of his research, where he studied and tested various psychological and sociological theories on homosexuality. Found that most theories suggest that homosexuality is a superficial occurrence and could not prove any of the theories true. Homosexuality is actually deep-rooted and is the same as heterosexuality in its biological nature.
  - 14th National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference: The Impact of Homophobia & Ageism on Medical Care for Old Lesbians, 10 July 1992; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 12)
    Recording of workshop, "The Impact of Homophobia & Ageism on Medical Care for Old Lesbians," at the 14th NLGHC in Los Angeles, CA. Speakers from Old Lesbians Organizing for Change coalition, discuss issues arising in older lesbian communities, including family, retirement, health care, age, and sexuality.
  - Identifying and Challenging Ageism, 1992; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 13)
    Recording of workshop, "Identifying and Challenging Ageism," at CANA, in 1992 in Los Angeles, CA. The speaker is from the Old Lesbians Organizing for Change coalition, and she discusses aging, ageism, empowering lesbians to embrace aging, and the importance of establishing committees, networks, and outreach efforts that include audiences of persons of all ages.
    Cannot hear speakers in audience, only main workshop speaker.
  - KHSU Women's Show: Miscellaneous, 18 October 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 14)
    KHSU 90.5 Arcata September-October, 1987, Women's Shows: Reading & Music, excerpt from "Long Time Passing": Lives of Older Lesbians, edited by Marcy Adelman AND Lesbian Concert
  - Leisure World, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 15)
    Recording of an interview with a representative from Leisure World Community Center. Discuss neighborhood, buildings/architecture, real estate, church congregations, population, and other general information about Leisure World. Followed by recording of advertisement for Leisure World.
    Only the interviewer's voice is clearly audible.
  - Consumerism and Censorship, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 16)
    Interview with Leisure World Community representative continued. Also interview residents of Leisure World, Penny Pierce and Dominda Wood
- Spoken Alphabetized Speaker/Topic Cassettes, 1972-1995; Series 17.; 23 audio cassette tapes
  Audio recordings of music, literature, poetry, personal narratives, and self-help literature. Most of the items were professionally recorded, including material from Radical Rose Productions, Lily Tomlin, Cris Williamson, Mary Watkins, the Chicago Women's Liberation Rock Band, and the Michigan Womyn's Festival.
  - The Lesbian Frequency #1, A Journal on Cassette, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 1-2)
    Compilation by Radical Rose Productions in Minneapolis, Minnesota, one of a series of tapes created specifically for lesbians. Editors are J Haggard and Sidney Spinsters. Contents of this tape include, an introduction; "Dykes Flight Back," with Frederique Delacoste and Felice Newman; "My Lesbian Body," a song by Sidney Spinster; excerpt from "Coming Out: An Autobiography," by Toni A.H. McNaron; commentary by Becky Kent; "Who is Radical Rose," and an excerpt from the Minneapolis Jewish Lesbian Program.
    Audio tape slows and sounds warped at the beginning of tape. Copyright note: content and format of The Lesbian Frequency: a journal on cassette is copyright 1983 by Radical Rose Recordings.
  - The Lesbian Frequency #2, A Journal on Cassette, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 3-4)
    Compilation by Radical Rose Productions in Minneapolis, Minnesota, one of a series of tapes created specifically for lesbians. Editors are J Haggard and Sidney Spinsters. Contents of this tape include: "Dykes Fight Back," with Pam Richardson; "Against My Will," by M. Joyner Bullock; talk with Barbara Grier and Ann Bannon; interview with Merle Woo by Marj Schneider; "Sister," by M. Joyner Bullock; workshop with Alix Dobkin, entitled "Why We Need Woman-only Space;" and "Marshall's Tune," by Elaine Townsend.
    Condition note: Tape stops frequently. Majority of recording is unplayable. Copyright note: content and format of The Lesbian Frequency: a journal on cassette is copyright 1983 by Radical Rose Recordings.
  - Inner Woman, Inner Sanctuary, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 5)
    Narrated and written by Denise Linn. Linn is a teacher and writer, specializing in feng shui, space clearing, meditation, and personal energy. Arranged and recorded by David J. Hinz and Jeff Cifka. Flute player is David J. Hinz and the synthesizer is Jeff Cifka.
    Copyright notes: Denise Linn, 1983, and Wisdom Books, Inc., 1983.
  - Lesbian Bedtime Stories, 1995; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 6)
    Recorded by Fuhr/Noble Productions, seven lesbian erotica stories written and performed by Sharon Noble and Gayle Fuhr. Stories are accompanied by music that is composed and performed by Bob Fetherolf. List of stories: Dark Symphony, When the Fat Lady Sings, Ach'e Mebele, Strapped, Subway, Love Letters, and Ach'e Mebele Music.
    Copyright note: 1995 by Fuhr/Noble Productions
  - I'm in Love With Lesbians, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 7)
    Recording of interview with Maxine Feldman on December, 31, 1982 in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Maxine Feldman discuss her Jewish heritage, lesbian music, herstory, sexuality, and politics. Sidney Spinster and Marj Schneider are interviewers, and J haggard is the editor and recorder.
    Copyright notes: Radical Rose Recordings, 1983. Angry Atthis with Atthis Music, Atthis Publication, 1979.
  - A Few Loving Women, [ca. 1970s]; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 8)
    Possible recorded from a record, the album, "A Few Loving Women" was the first openly lesbian album. The album was recorded at the Firehouse in New York City, by members of the Lesbian Feminist Liberation group. Side 1: "I'd Like to Make Love to You," Margaret Sloan; "Edith," Martha and Lucy Wilde; "Gladys," Luci Wilde; "Big Orgasm," Roberta Kosse; "Funny Lady," Lee Crespi; "What are you doing today," Lee Crespi; and "Women Like Me," Roberta Kosse. Side 2: "Through Your Blue Veil," Jeriann Hilderly; "Cubicle," Ali; "Big Orgasm," Roberta Kosse; "You'd Be Surprised," Roberta Kosse; "Where Are You Going?" Mary M. Solberg; and "I'd Like to Make Love With You," Margaret Sloan.
  - Dykes Resist! First Hand Accounts of Lesbians Fighting Male Violence., 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 9)
    Compilation by Radical Rose Recordings of personal accounts of Lesbians who helped stop male violence. Tape includes: "Against My Will," M. Joyner Bullock; an interview with Julie Fullmoon Joy; stories by Terri L .Jewell with comments by Laura Rose; a story by Randi Randolph; and a discussion with Felice Newman, Frederique Delacoste, J Haggard and Pam Richardson.
    Tape is unplayable. Copyright note: Copyright 1983 by Radical Rose Recordings
  - Discussion following Lesbian Masquerade Showing, 11/24/1970; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 10)
    Discussion following Lesbian Masquerade showing in Los Angeles. The event was organized by the San Francisco Lesbian and Gay History Project. Lesbian Masquerade is an illustrated lecture by Allan Berube about women passed as men in 19th-century San Francisco.
  - Spiderwoman - A Celebration of Women Heroes, 1968; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 1)
    Recording from live presentation at Euphoria Sound in Revere, Massachusetts, September 1986. The stories bring together traditional elements and feminist ideas. Jennifer Justice is the storyteller of all the stories, which are: The Jugglers, Lia, Spiderwoman, The Last Panther in Eastern Kentucky.
    Copyright note: Moon Star Stories, 1986.
  - Moon Rabbit: An Astrological Look Into 1984, audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 2)
    Recording of Moon Rabbit describing astrology got 1984, including Pluto's entrance in Scorpio and Neptune's move into Capricorn. Also, how 1984's cycles will affect those born early, mid or late in each sign. Moon Rabbit has studied, taught, and practiced astrology in the Minneapolis-St. Paul area since 1974. The recording was edited by J Haggard.
    Copyright note: Radical Rose Recordings, 1984.
  - Lumiere, A Science Fantasy Fable, 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 3)
    Originally released in 1978, the story and music ware by Cris Williamson. In the story, X-Ray Ted, a little boy, discovers 'an extraordinary world' inside his closet. He and his dog Sirius encounter an entire universe and travel extensively through space, meeting strange creatures. Cris Williamson is an American feminist singer-songwriter and a lesbian political activist.
    Copyright note: Pacific Cascade Records, 1982.
  - We Were All Outlaws: A Lesbian Oral Herstory By K Krepps, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 4)
    Lesbian herstory interview of with K Krepps. Krepps was out as a lesbian in the 1950s and 1960s. She discusses her early life, significant experiences, and relationships during those decades. Sidney Spinster is the editor.
    Copyright note: Radical Rose Recordings, 1984
  - We Are Among You: Lesbians with Disabilities, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 5-6)
    Recording of of Lesbian and gay disability group meeting at A Woman's Coffeehouse in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Kim, Candi, Pat, Mari and Alison organized and are speakers at the meeting. Recorded by Sidney Spinster.
  - Flying Thunder Cloud: Talking About Myself, 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 7)
    Flying Thunder discusses parenting, being institutionalized, lesbian separatism, and relationships.
    Copyright Note: Radical Rose Recordings, 1984
  - Lily Tomlin: On Stage, 1977; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 8)
    On Stage is a performance, starring Lily Tomlin, conceived and produced by Jane Wagner. From the Broadway show "Appearing Nightly." Written And directed by Jane Wagner And Lily Tomlin. Lily Tomlin is an American actress, comedian, writer, and producer. Track list: Mr. Theater Goer And Shopping Bag Lady, Mrs. Judith Beasley (Unnatural Resources, Lud And Marie Meet Dracula's Daughter (A Tale Of Teen-age Tyranny), Ernestine (Phone Company Commercial), Tell Miss Sweeney Goodbye, Shopping Bag Lady And UFO Guy, Glenna - A Child Of The 60's, Lily And Shopping Bag Lady.
    Copyright note: 1977 Arista Records, INC.
  - Lily Tomlin: The Search for Intelligent Life in the Universe, 1991; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 9)
    Audio recording of film version of Lily Tomlin's one-woman performance. Written by Jane Wagner and performed by Lily Tomlin. Lily Tomlin is an American actress, comedian, writer, and producer.
  - Mary Watkins Demo: Spiritsong, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 10)
    Recording of Mary Watkins' musical album, Spiritsong. Tracks include: Comin' Home, Mirrors, Playground, Manhattan Mist, Spiritsong, Moonlight Chapel, Changing Seasons. Mary Watkins is a folk, new age, and instrumental musical artist.
    Note on tape: "Do not duplicate"
  - Gertrude Stein Reads, 1972; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 11)
    Recording of Gertrude Stein reading her poetry and prose. Tracks include: The Making of Americans: Parts 1 and 2; A Valentine to Sherwood Anderson; If I Told Him: A Completed Portrait of Picasso/Matisse; and Madame Recaimer: An Opera. Born in Pennsylvania in 1874, Gertrude Stein attended Radcliffe College, where she studied psychology under the great William James. Stein settled in Paris where she began experimenting with writing techniques and before long became an important literary figure in the Parisian art world of her day. Gertrude Stein also helped launch the careers of artists and influenced and entertained the writers, Hemingway, Pound and Fitzgerald in her famous Paris salon. Gertrude Stein died in Neuilly-sur-Seine in 1946.
    Copyright note: Caedmon, 1972
  - Mountain Moving Day, [ca. 1970s]; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 12)
    Mountain Moving Say is an album by the Chicago and New Haven Women's Liberation Rock Bands. The Chicago Women's Liberation Rock Band was the musical expression of the Chicago Women's Liberation Union, an early feminist organization. The Chicago Women's Liberation Uniion was formed in 1969, and the band soon after.
  - 10th Annual Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 13)
    Live album recording of the 10th Annual Michigan Womyn's Music Festival. The Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, also referred to as MWMF or Michfest, is an international feminist music festival occurring every August since 1976 near Hart, Michigan, in a small wooded area in northern Oceana County, Michigan. The event is completely built, staffed, run and attended by women.
- Autobiography - In the Best Interest, 1976-1986; Series 6.; 49 audio cassette tapes
  Interviews with lesbians, recordings of lesbian group meetings about issues such as motherhood, lesbian history, lesbian literature and lesbian life more generally. Includes interviews with Del Martin and Phyllis Lyon, Monika Kehoe, and Marion Zimmer Bradley.
  - #1 Auto/Biography Martin, Del Lyon, Phyllis Interview, 7 August 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 1-2)
  - #3 Auto/Biography Reid, Ruth "Dark Birth" Selections, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 3)
    Ruth Reid reads selections for "in the life." Copy of reel to reel.
  - #4 Auto/Biography Vargas, Michaela Interview, 31 August 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 4-5)
  - #5 Auto/Biography Nichols, R. Staggs, J. Interview, August 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 6-7)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 1 "In the Best Interests..." Orange County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 2 "In the Best Interests..." Orange County Women, undated (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 3 "In the best interests..." Cotati County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 10)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 4 "In the best interests..." Nancy and Paula, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 11)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 5 "In the best interests..." Nancy and Paula, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 12)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 7 "In the best interests..." Los Angeles Mother's Group, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 13)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 8 "In the best interests..." Los Angeles Mother's Group, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 14)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 9 "In the best interests..." Susan and Margaret, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 15)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 10 "In the best interests..." Susan and Margaret, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 16)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 11 "In the best interests..." Margaret, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 17)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 12 "In the best interests..." Margaret, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 18)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 13 "In the best interests" Santa Barbara County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 14 "In the best interests..." Santa Barbara County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 15 "In the best interests..." Santa Barbara County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 16 "In the best interests..." Santa Barbara County Women, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 17 "In the best interests..." Pat, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 18 "In the best interests..." Sassy, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 19 "In the best interests..." Elana, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 20 "In the best interests..." Evelyn, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 21 "In the best interests..." Paula, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 9)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 22 "In the best interests..." Peggy and Elaine, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 10)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 23 "In the best interests..." Marlene, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 11)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 24 "In the best interests..." Nancy, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 12)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 25 "In the best interests..." Yvonne, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 13)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 26 "In the best interests..." Karen, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 14)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 27 "In the best interests..." Shirley, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 15)
  - #7 Auto/Biography Tape 28 "In the best interests..." Judge Jerry Pacht, 19 April 1976; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 16)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 3 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - Stein, etc.", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 17)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 4 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - Singles...", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 18)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 5 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - 1955-1965", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 6 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - Young Ones...", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 7 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - Fiction", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - #9 Auto/Biography Tape 8 of 8 Taylor, Valerie "Our Lesbian Roots - Poetry", 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - #10 Auto/Biography Kehoe, Monika - Interview, 17 December 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - #13 Auto/Bio Tape 1 of 1 M.Z. Bradley "Personal Note", 1978; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - #14 Auto/Bio Tape 3 of 3 J. Phelps and B. MacCulloch, April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - #15 Auto/Bio Tape 1 of 2 Ann Bannon Interview, June 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - #16 Auto/Bio 1 Tape Peg Cruikshank, Martin Wojewoda Lesb/Gay Literature Class, 24 January 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 9)
  - #17 Auto/Bio 1 Tape Peg Cruikshank, Dan Allen Lesbian/Gay Lit Class, 22 April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 10)
  - #18 Auto/Bio 1 Tape Marie Kuda talks on lesbian bio. Gay Academic Union, 9 October 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 11)